hi mom all good
I am a supervisor
ha ha ha
my god i am
and today is day twenty-two
ha ha now I'm waiting
that guy from the proposal I got
is on
we combined to be here at the gas station
and I'm waiting right
I'm giving a shit over there on my cameras
we go together
1 short express knows
the stronger one
yes there
it's the most spacious Chevette you'll ever walk
oh Leo
we're going to go in gear there,
it's already late.
I don't know what you think of your life there uncle
but today I wanted to say that I'm
because I became a supervisor
that's not right Léo
that's it bro
and now i have to get out of here
and there in front several points
here are ten people i have to oversee
bro then i have to look at all the work
photograph to send report to customer
then how are you
let me ask you something you passed
protector
you're drinking water Gil
for you
God bless
tamo together
and it's all been here
I'm here with Raíssa
yael sunscreen
valeu
time this stuff here Guy
it is ecological
the opportunity sometimes you don't have
but you're the one who has to create guy
hour strip
what is your name John
thank you John is us
I didn't see your car for him
it's the time
bike wants to switch on the comb
we now on the needle
ah but i'll have to go back to that something
back another fifty thousand
ok bro
tamo together
you have to give structure to your collaborator bro
it's the least you can do too
gives a good condition for that person too
deliver the pamphlet and thank you there
from the heart
thank you brother
if you want another opportunity
send me a message
it's on that I'm available
see it's us malandro let's go let's go uncle
tomorrow i will use 1 strategy that i call
Trojan horse
tamo together